

# **Roderick Moise**

Designer & Developer

W: rmoise.com Github: /rmoise Linkedin: /roderickmoise

E: roderickfmoise@gmail.com

A: Berlin, DE

## **Profile**

From Brooklyn to Berlin, my career blends NYC ad agency experience with a passion for Bauhaus-inspired design. I recently completed a full-stack web development bootcamp at CareerFoundry, where I built my own website. I aim to create seamless, user-focused experiences.

# **Experience**

#### 2023 - 2024

## UI / UX Designer

## KARL STORZ Berlin, Germany

- Designed landing pages and email templates for KARL STORZ with Figma, enhancing brand and engagement.
- Used Figma to design website components/templates in Opentext CMS and Salesforce. Improved online catalog UX
- · Conducted competitor research and user journey mapping, offering insights to inform product development and design decisions for the online catalog.

#### 2019 - 2022

## **UI / Brand Designer**

Kyto Berlin, Germany

- · Created a cohesive brand strategy for Kyto, a software as a service company, and new products.
- Created new visual identity, including marketing materials and UI for web and mobile apps, ensuring brand consistency.
- New branding, website, and mobile design boosted customer engagement, leading to Müller Medien acquisition.

#### 2018

## Product / Brand Designer

Smunch Berlin, Germany

- Implemented a customer-centric product and brand design strategy for Smunch, a food delivery startup.
- · Conducted user research to identify pain points, enhance UX, and update visual identity for promotions.
- Achieved a 156% increase in mobile sessions and up to 2% increase in conversion rates post-launch.

## **Education**

## CareerFoundry

Full Stack Dev Certificate Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

## **Fashion Institute of Technology**

BFA in Graphic Design Aug 2013 - May 2015 NY, NY

## Languages

English: Native German: Beginner

Haitian Creole: Intermediate

## **Skills**

TypeScript C# Firebase UI/L Bootstrap ASP.NET Heroku Bra React PostgreSQL Netlify Prot Angular MongoDB Postman Use	obe CC ma UX Design and Identity ototyping er Research ability

# **Roderick Moise**

Designer & Developer

A: Berlin, DE

W: rmoise.com E: roderickfmoise@gmail.com

Github: /rmoise Linkedin: /roderickmoise

# **Projects**

### 2023

### **Document Management App**

## Personal Project

- · Developed a React and ASP.NET Core document management app with upload, preview, sharing, using PostgreSQL and Azure Blob Storage.
- · Added secure authentication and responsive design for all devices.
- Deployed on Azure, including user guides for easy adoption.

#### 2023

### **Meet App**

#### CareerFoundry

- Developed a PWA in React to display events from Google Calendar.
- Applied TDD with Jest (unit), Cucumber (acceptance), and Puppeteer (E2E) tests based on user stories.
- · Implemented serverless functions using AWS Lambda and used a Kanban board to follow an agile process.

#### 2022

### myFlix

### CareerFoundry

- Created a non-relational movie database (MongoDB) and built a REST API with Node.JS and Express.
- Tested the API endpoints with Postman, wrote clean and concise documentation, deployed the API with Heroku.
- Designed and developed two single-page, responsive frontend applications using React and Angular.